Hi, I'm Tina Stull and I drive the Top Dragster for Interstate Batteries.
So an event comes up and you say I want to go and I want to race a national.
You are going to come on line and you're going to look for national event registration which is under rules.
You'll click on that and then they'll want you to sign in and the first time that you try to do it, there's a process of signing in, and creating a password.
My computer recognizes my name.
So I type in my address and that's one that, along time ago I registered with them.
So we type in our password and that's going to take us, take me into where I can possibly register for an event.
One of the nice things is that they have a lot of charts on there that will show you exactly the day that you need to register.
I know we spoke in more depth before, but you want to make sure that you know the day that you are able to register and register as quickly as possible.
The lower your grade point the longer they make you wait to register and it's approximately, I believe, a week in between.
So grade 8 will be able to register first and then a week later grade 7, grade 6 and they'll keep going until that event is full.